GRANT SOLOMON

+1 229.223.6488 ♦ gsolo2001@outlook.com Portfolio Website—gsolo2001.github.io

PROFILE

I am a dedicated IT professional with B.S. in Computer Science from Valdosta State University.

I have three years of experience working in Valdosta State's IT help desk, where my responsibilities as IT help desk manager included troubleshooting a variety of technical issues, managing user accounts, creating a knowledge base, and IT training for both help desk agents and university faculty and staff. In addition to my help desk role, I also served as the system administrator for our university's work order system (Ivanti Neurons for ITSM) where I was in charge of system design and updates.

My passion is to equip ministry leaders with the technology to transform lives by the truth of Christ.

EDUCATION

B.S. in Computer Science - magna cum laude

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

May 2022

EXPERIENCE

Assistant AV Technician

March 2023 - til date

New Covenant Church - Valdosta, GA

- Internship under the AV director of my church
- My primary purpose is to learn more about AV in ministry and become familiar with all the technologies involved

Shop Manager

March 2023 - til date

Event Point - Valdosta, GA

- Event Point is a production company that focuses on audio, video, and lighting setups for corporate events
- I'm responsible for the prep/deprep, cataloging, maintenance, and overall upkeep for all of our AV equipment

IT Help Desk Manager

Aug 2021 - March 2023

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- System Administrator for VSU's work order system (Ivanti Neurons for ITSM)
- Manage the hiring, training, and supervision of all help desk technicians

Web Development Internship

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- Created a website for the Southwest Georgia Healthcare Partnership
- Learned how to manage and work with clients

IT Help Desk Technician

Feb 2020 - Aug 2021

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- Tasked with assisting faculty, staff, and students with technology issues
- Provided IT support, knowledge, and training for all help desk agents